OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN.
DON'T FORGET THAT TOMORROW
IS THE DAY
EMILY GETS MARRIED AGAIN
SO, WHATEVER WE DO
JUST TRY TO REALLY
KEEP ROSS'S MIND OFF OF IT.
OH, YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
HEY, MAN, WHAT'S UP?
OH, JUST THINKING ABOUT EMILY
GETTING MARRIED TOMORROW.
OH, ROSS, LOOK! LOOK!
WHAT? WHERE?
RIGHT OVER THERE.
RIGHT THERE.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
SOMEBODY HELP ME OUT HERE.
HEY.
HELLO.
HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
MONICA, SORRY I DIDN'T
COME BY LAST NIGHT.
I WAS OUT WITH GARY.
HE LET ME RIDE
AROUND WITH HIM
IN HIS COP CAR.
WE SAW AND
PREVENTED CRIMES.
YOU GOT TO GO
ON A RIDE-ALONG?
UH-HUH.
I WANT TO GO ON A RIDE-ALONG.
ME, TOO.
OKAY.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
REALLY? YOU?
YEAH.
I MEAN,
IT'S KIND OF DANGEROUS.
WELL, I LIKE DANGER.
OKAY, YOU GUYS FREE TONIGHT?
YEAH.
TONIGHT? Y-YOU DIDN'T SAY
IT WAS GOING
TO BE AT NIGHTTIME.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY.
I THOUGHT TONIGHT
WE COULD FINALLY ORGANIZE
THESE PHOTOS.
OH, THANK GOD!
FINALLY!
OKAY.
I'VE BROKEN THEM DOWN
INTO CATEGORIES, OKAY?
WE HAVE, UH,
WE GOT HOLIDAYS,
BIRTHDAYS, CANDIDS.
AND THEN WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I'VE CROSS-REFERENCED THEM
BY SUBJECT, RIGHT?
SO IF YOU'RE
LOOKING UP
LET'S SAY,
"BIRTHDAYS" AND "DOGS"
YOU GET PHOTO 152. SEE?
OH, IT'S ME AND LAPOOH.
WOW, I MISS THAT DOG.
WELL, YOU CAN ALSO FIND HIM
UNDER "DOG" AND "DEAD."
GREAT, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT.
HAND ME THAT OTHER
BOX OF PHOTOS.
THAT'S THE VERY LAST ONE.
OKAY.
( screams )
OOPS.
SORRY.
WELL, GOOD THING
YOU NUMBERED ALL OF THEM, HUH?
I HADN'T.
PHOTO 152 WAS A PROTOTYPE.
OH, HONEY, HONEY, HONEY,
IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
HONEY, HOW ABOUT
I FIX YOU A DRINK, HUH?
MAYBE A MARGARITA?
ROSS HAS
THE BLENDER.
OH, EVERYTHING'S
JUST FALLING APART.
NO, HONEY, IT'S OKAY.
LISTEN, I'LL GO TO ROSS'S,
GET THE BLENDER.
YOU GET
ALL THE MARGARITA STUFF READY.
HIS KEYS ARE IN THE DRAWER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
ALSO, I NEED SOME CASH.
YOU WANT ME TO STOP
AT THE A.T.M.?
NO. WHILE YOU'RE AT ROSS'S,
IF YOU SEE ANY LYING AROUND.
WHAT?
WHAT? I-I-I DON'T,
I DON'T DO THAT.
THAT WAS SO COOL, MAN,
THAT WAY YOU LEANED ON THAT GUY.
IT IS STARTING
TO GET DARK OUT THERE.
HE TOLD YOU EVERYTHING.
I MEAN,
YOU TOTALLY CRACKED HIM.
YEAH, WELL, BEING
THAT HE WAS THE VICTIM.
THEY'RE USUALLY
PRETTY TALKATIVE.
OKAY, BUT IT IS OFFICIALLY
NIGHTTIME.
ALL RIGHT, GARY, DO YOU WANT ME
TO GRAB THE BERRY FOR YOU?
IT'S CALLED A CHERRY.
CHANDLER!
( laughing )
OKAY.
I GOT IT.
THIS PLACE MAKES
THE BEST SANDWICH IN THE WORLD.
HEY, JOE, DOES IT
HAVE MEATBALLS ON IT?
OH, YEAH.
MELTED CHEESE AND
MARINARA SAUCE?
YUP.
YEAH, YOU CAN'T EAT
THAT IN MY CAR.
YEAH, OKAY.
EVEN THOUGH MY TAX DOLLARS
PAID FOR THIS CAR.
YOUR TAX DOLLARS?
YEAH, OKAY.
WOW, THAT SANDWICH
REALLY DOES SMELL GOOD.
DID I SAY
YOU COULD SMELL IT?
I CAN'T SMELL YOUR SANDWICH?
HALF THE TASTE
IS IN THE SMELL.
YOU'RE SUCKING UP
ALL THE TASTE UNITS.
OKAY, I'LL GIVE THEM BACK.
( blowing air out nose )
WHAT IS SO GREAT
ABOUT THAT SANDWICH?
OKAY, IMAGINE
THE BEST SEX YOU EVER HAD.
OKAY.
ARE YOU THINKING
ABOUT MONICA?
YEAH.
YEAH, WHAT'S THAT LIKE?
( yells )
OH, PLEASE DON'T BE
FROM A REAL DINOSAUR.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
"MADE IN MEXICO." YES!
OH. WHO WOULD BUY THIS?
OH.
( phone ringing )
Monica:
Rach, it's me. Pick up.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
I need a few more things
to make the margaritas.
UM, I NEED SOME, UH, SOME SALT,
SOME MARGARITA MIX, AND TEQUILA.
SO ALL WE HAD WAS ICE?
SEE IF HE HAS ICE.
OKAY.
( phone ringing )
( beeping )
Hello, Ross?
It's Emily here.
I know this is out of the blue,
but, um
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Well... maybe I am.
I keep thinking about you
and I'm wondering
if we made a mistake
giving up so fast.
Are you thinking about me?
No, of course you're not.
But if you are, call me tonight.
Okay, bye.
OH! OH!
Ross:
SO, WHERE WE GOING NEXT?
THIS WITNESS WON'T
RETURN MY CALLS
SO WE'RE GOING TO SEE
IF WE CAN SURPRISE
HIM COMING HOME.
S-SURPRISE HIM?
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO MAKE ANYBODY
MAD, ARE WE?
COME ON, MAN.
SO, YOU GOING TO SQUEEZE
THE PERP'S SHOES A LITTLE BIT
BEFORE HE LAWYERS UP?
IT'S A WITNESS, NOT A PERP,
AND NO ONE TALKS LIKE THAT.
YEAH, NO ONE TALKS LIKE THAT.
OH, WHAT? LIKE YOU'RE MR. COP?
HEY, I'M MORE COP
THAN YOU TWO.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THAT?
HELLO.
I'M IN
THE FRONT SEAT, OKAY.
I'M GARY'S PARTNER.
YOU KNOW, WHEN
YOU SAY "PARTNER"
IT DOESN'T SOUND COP.
IT SOUNDS GAY.
UM, JEALOUS.
HEY, DO YOU MIND?
WE'RE UNDERCOVER HERE.
OH, YEAH. NO PROBLEM.
ROSS.
SORRY, SORRY.
THERE.
HEY, GARY, WHO AM I?
( imitating E.T. ):
PHONE HOME.
LOOK AT OFFICER ROSS
RIDING BACK HERE
WITH THE VISITORS.
YEAH, WHAT'S UP WITH THAT,
SERPICO?
Emily:
Are you thinking about me?
No, of course you're not.
But if you are, call me tonight.
Okay, bye.
NO!
I KNOW.
WELL, THANK GOD
YOU WERE HERE.
I MEAN, WE HAVE
TO ERASE THAT.
WHAT? WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WE HAVE TO.
WHAT IF ROSS HEARS THAT,
AND THEN CALLS HER BACK
AND THEN THEY GET
BACK TOGETHER?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT--
ROSS BACK WITH
THAT CONTROLLING
NEUROTIC, CRAZY EMILY?
EMILY THAT WOULDN'T
LET HIM SEE YOU?
NO! OH, NO. NO. GOD, NO.
HE SHOULD NOT GET BACK TOGETHER
WITH HER.
I MEAN, I KNOW THAT,
YOU KNOW THAT
EVEN ROSS KNOWS THAT.
BUT THAT STILL DOESN'T GIVE US
THE RIGHT TO ERASE HIS MESSAGE.
LOOK, I'M HIS SISTER,
OKAY? AND I LOVE HIM.
I DON'T WANT TO
SEE HIM GET HURT.
COME ON, DOESN'T THAT GIVE ME
THE RIGHT TO CONTROL HIM...?
HELP HIM?
I DON'T THINK
HE'S THE ONE WHO NEEDS HELP.
LOOK. SHE'S OBVIOUSLY
UNSTABLE, OKAY?
SHE'S THINKING ABOUT
RUNNING OUT ON
HER WEDDING DAY.
OKAY, FINE.
BUT LOOK AT THE POSITION
SHE'S PUTTING HIM IN.
WHAT'S HE'S GOING TO DO?
ROSS IS GOING TO RUN OVER
THERE ON THE WEDDING DAY
AND BREAK UP THE MARRIAGE?
I MEAN, WHO WOULD DO THAT?
OKAY, FINE. ALL RIGHT?
BUT, THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
ALTHOUGH IT DID INVOLVE
A LOT OF THE SAME PEOPLE.
OH...!
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
SOME TWISTED JOKE SHE'S
TRYING TO PLAY ON HIM.
OKAY, YOU ARE CRAZY.
I'M SORRY,
BUT SHE SOUNDED GENUINELY UPSET.
I MEAN, LISTEN.
Male voice:
Your messages have been erased.
NO!
OKAY, BUT YOU KNOW,
W-WE'RE SAFE, RIGHT?
I MEAN, NOTHING BAD
IS GOING TO GO DOWN?
Gary:
NO.
BUT THAT REMINDS ME.
SIGN THIS.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S NOTHING.
IT SAYS YOU CAN'T
SUE THE CITY
IF YOU SCRAPE YOUR KNEE
OR, YOU KNOW, GET
YOUR HEAD BLOWN OFF.
OH, HURRY UP.
I WANT TO SIGN THAT.
OKAY, HERE HE COMES.
Gary:
WHAT IS HE DOING?
WHAT THE HELL IS HE DOING?
WHAT IS IT?
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OKAY, HE SEES US.
DON'T MOVE.
AND DON'T LOOK
AT HIM.
( loud bang )
HEY, IT'S OKAY.
IT WAS JUST A
CAR BACKFIRE.
HEY, LOOK AT THAT.
YOU TRIED TO SAVE YOUR BUDDY.
YOU SEE THAT?
YOU SEE
WHAT HE DID?
YOU OKAY, MAN?
UH-HUH.
THANKS, JOEY.
UH, HELLO!
HI?
I GUESS WE SHOULD GO.
NO. WAIT, WAIT.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
NO. MONICA...
MONICA, WE HAVE TO FIX THIS.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
YOU'VE ERASED THE MESSAGE.
YEAH, WELL, UNLESS WE TELL HIM.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
TOTALLY RATIONAL ABOUT THIS
I CAN'T ARGUE WITH YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
FINE. IF YOU WANT TO TELL HIM,
TELL HIM.
I JUST,
I DON'T WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
( phone ringing )
OH! MAYBE THAT'S EMILY
CALLING BACK
TO LEAVE THE EXACT SAME MESSAGE.
Ross:
Hey, Ross, it's you.
I just want you
to remember this feeling.
You are lucky to be alive
so live every day
to the fullest.
Love yourself, okay? Okay.
Oh, and also, get stamps. Bye.
WOW.
PLAY THAT MESSAGE FOR EMILY
AND THIS WHOLE PROBLEM
GOES AWAY.
OH, RIGHT.
HEY, ANYBODY WANT
TO MEET A HERO?
JOHN GLENN IS HERE?
NO, JOEY.
PHEEBS, WE HAD THE
MOST INCREDIBLE NIGHT.
OKAY, SO, WE'RE
IN THE CAR...
WAIT, HOLD ON.
HI.
OKAY, GO AHEAD.
OKAY, OKAY
SO, WE'RE IN
THE CAR, RIGHT?
AND BANG! A SHOT WAS FIRED
AND JOEY, WITH NO REGARD
FOR HIS OWN SAFETY
THROWS HIMSELF ON ME.
OH, MY GOD, JOEY.
IT WAS A CAR BACKFIRE.
YEAH, BUT HE
DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
YEAH, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
AND IT COULD HAVE JUST AS EASILY
HAVE BEEN A BULLET.
HEY, JOEY, EVER THINK
ABOUT JOINING THE FORCE?
WE COULD USE
A GUY LIKE YOU.
WHO JUMPS AT LOUD NOISES.
WOW.
I COULD HAVE DIED TONIGHT.
YEAH, IF THE CAR THAT BACKFIRED
HAD RUN OVER YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO
HOME BEFORE ROSS
STARTS RAMBLING
ABOUT HIS NEWFOUND
RESPECT FOR LIFE.
I DO HAVE
A NEWFOUND RESPECT FOR LIFE.
OH, MY GOD.
SO, YOU WANT
TO GET SOME DINNER?
YEAH, SURE.
YEAH.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF I HEARD A SHOT RIGHT NOW,
I'D THROW MY BODY ON YOU.
OH, YEAH? WELL,
MAYBE YOU AND I
SHOULD TAKE A WALK
IN A BAD NEIGHBORHOOD.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
BYE.
CUT IT OUT, ROSS.
I'D HATE TO HAVE
TO SAVE YOUR LIFE
AND KICK YOUR ASS
IN THE SAME DAY.
DUDE?
HOW COME YOU TOOK OFF?
OH, JUST GOING FOR A WALK.
AROUND THE LIVING ROOM.
WHATEVER.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
NO. NO, I'M JUST TIRED.
YOU KNOW, FROM THE WALK.
OH. OKAY.
YOU DOVE IN FRONT OF ROSS.
ROSS.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
OH, MY GOD. YOU HATE ROSS.
I DON'T HATE ROSS.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
I SAVED HIM.
YOU'RE MAD AT ME.
IT ALL ADDS UP.
YOU WANT ROSS OUT
OF THE PICTURE.
WHAT PICTURE?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I DON'T LIKE
WHAT I'M HEARING.
LOOK, I'M VERY GLAD
THAT YOU SAVED ROSS
FROM THE CAR BACKFIRE
BUT IT COULD HAVE BEEN
A BULLET
AND, YOU KNOW,
YOU DIDN'T TRY TO SAVE ME.
OH.
YOU'RE UPSET BECAUSE
YOU THINK I CHOSE
ROSS OVER YOU.
NO. I KNEW YOU COULD
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, ROSS, HE NEEDS HELP.
HE'S NOT STREET LIKE US.
COME ON, WHAT IT COMES DOWN TO
IS YOU WOULD RISK YOUR LIFE
FOR ROSS
BEFORE YOU WOULD FOR ME.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
N-NO, NOT EXACTLY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK. I...
I WASN'T TRYING TO SAVE ROSS
OKAY?
MY SANDWICH WAS NEXT TO ROSS.
ALL RIGHT?
I WA... I WAS TRYING
TO SAVE MY SANDWICH.
FROM A BULLET?
I KNOW
IT DOESN'T MAKE MUCH SENSE.
MUCH SENSE?
CHANDLER, IT WAS INSTINCT, OKAY?
I JUST WENT FOR IT.
SO YOU RISKED YOUR LIFE
FOR A SANDWICH?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY,
BUT, CHANDLER
THIS IS THE GREATEST SANDWICH
IN THE WORLD.
SO YOU DIDN'T, UH,
CHOOSE ROSS BEFORE ME?
NO. I WOULD
NEVER DO THAT.
YOU'RE LIKE MY BROTHER.
REALLY?
YEAH. IN FACT
TO PROVE HOW MUCH
YOU MEAN TO ME...
HERE.
THANKS.
OH, EASY, IT'S NOT A HOT DOG.
HOW GOOD IS THAT?
( garbled ):
OH, YEAH.
SEE?
MM-HMM.
OH, DUDE, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SHOWING ME
HOW MUCH I MEAN TO YOU.
YEAH. WITH A BITE.
( chuckling ):
GEEZ!
( keys jingling )
HEY, HI.
RACH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE IN OUR APARTMENT
ALL THE TIME, OKAY?
THIS IS JUST A DROP
IN THE BUCKET, MISTER.
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THE IMPORTANT THING
IS THAT YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND,
AND YOU'RE HERE.
HUH. OKAY.
JUST A LITTLE SCARED.
WHAT'S GOING ON, ROSS?
THE MOST AMAZING THING
HAPPENED TONIGHT.
I THOUGHT MY NUMBER WAS UP.
I HAD AN ACTUAL
NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCE.
WHAT?! WHAT HAPPENED?
WE WERE ON THE RIDE-ALONG
WITH GARY, RIGHT?
AND SOMEBODY TOOK A SHOT AT ME.
( gasping )
REALLY?
NO, A CAR BACKFIRED, BUT...
I THOUGHT SOMEBODY WAS
TAKING A SHOT AT ME
AND, RACH, I, I SURVIVED.
AND I WAS
FILLED WITH
THIS, THIS GREAT
RESPECT FOR LIFE.
YOU KNOW, I WANT TO
EXPERIENCE EVERY MOMENT.
I WANT TO SEIZE
EVERY OPPORTUNITY.
I AM SEEING EVERYTHING
SO, SO CLEARLY NOW.
BECAUSE A CAR BACKFIRED?
OKAY, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS FITS
INTO YOUR WHOLE SEIZING THING
BUT, UM, EMILY CALLED YOU TODAY.
YOU TALKED TO HER?
NO, SHE LEFT
A MESSAGE.
BUT IT KIND OF GOT ERASED.
I MEAN, THERE'S...
SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR MACHINE.
OKAY, WHAT DID SHE SAY?
WELL, UM, SOMETHING
ABOUT HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS
ABOUT THE WEDDING
AND DID YOU GUYS MAKE A MISTAKE
BREAKING UP, AND, UH
SHE WANTS YOU TO CALL HER.
WOW.
NOW THAT WAS A GOOD THING
THAT I TOLD YOU, RIGHT?
HUH? YEAH. YES.
OF COURSE.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, BECAUSE
I'M GOING TO JUST GO TELL MONICA
THAT I WAS RIGHT.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE DIDN'T WANT...
NOT IMPORTANT.
THE POINT IS, I WAS RIGHT.
YOUR DECISION.
OKAY? I WAS RIGHT.
RIGHT.
I GUESS I SHOULD CALL EMILY.
OKAY. NO,
THAT'S NOT THE RIGHT DECISION.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
ROSS, COME ON.
I MEAN, THAT WOMAN
MADE YOU MISERABLE.
OKAY, ROSS
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO
GET BACK INTO THAT?
OKAY, LOOK, YESTERDAY
I WOULDN'T HAVE EVEN CONSIDERED
CALLING HER BACK
BUT MY EX-WIFE CALLS
ON THE SAME DAY
I HAVE A NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCE?
I MEAN, THAT'S GOT
TO MEAN SOMETHING, RIGHT?
ROSS, THAT WAS NOT A
NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCE.
THAT WAS BARELY
AN EXPERIENCE.
YOU WEREN'T THERE.
OKAY, MAYBE THIS IS SOMETHING
I'M SUPPOSED TO SEIZE, YOU KNOW?
OKAY. YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE THIS IS NOT
ABOUT SEIZING STUFF.
MAYBE THIS IS ABOUT
ESCAPING STUFF.
OKAY, I MEAN,
LOOK AT TODAY.
I MEAN, YOU ESCAPED...
DEATH...
YOU KNOW?
AND MAYBE THIS
IS A CHANCE FOR
YOU TO ESCAPE
GETTING BACK TOGETHER
WITH EMILY.
THAT DOES MAKE SENSE.
BECAUSE I DO
WANT TO SEIZE SOME OPPORTUNITY
BUT I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO SEE OR TALK TO HER.
THEN, THERE YOU GO.
YEAH.
YEAH, MAYBE TODAY'S JUST...
CLOSE CALL DAY.
HEY, THANKS, RACH.
OH, HONEY, NO PROBLEM.
OKAY.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THE MESSAGE IS BLINKING.
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T ERASE IT.
OH?
Hey, Ross, it's you.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S AN OLD MESSAGE.
NOBODY NEEDS TO HEAR THAT.
HEY, UM, WAS MONICA HERE?
YEAH.
YEAH, I WANT MY MONEY BACK.
YEAH, UM, YOU PROBABLY NEED THAT
FOR STAMPS, RIGHT?
HAS GARY EVER BEEN SHOT AT
FOR REAL?
YES, ONCE.
YEAH.
A LITTLE.
HE KIND OF DID IT TO HIMSELF.
IT'S NOT REALLY A GOOD STORY.
I WONDER HOW I'D REACT
UNDER FIRE, YOU KNOW?
AND NOT BACKFIRE,
BUT HEAVY FIRE.
LIKE IF I WAS IN A WAR
OR SOMETHING.
MAN, I WOULD BE
GREAT IN A WAR.
I MEAN, I THINK I WOULD MAKE
A FANTASTIC MILITARY LEADER.
I MEAN, I KNOW I
WOULD MAKE GENERAL
BEFORE ANY OF YOU GUYS.
BEFORE OR AFTER YOU WERE SHOT
BY YOUR OWN TROOPS?
I KNOW WHERE JOEY WOULD BE.
HE'D BE IN THE FOXHOLE
PROTECTING
ALL OF US.
YES, IF THE FOXHOLE
WAS LINED WITH SANDWICHES.
YEAH, HERO SANDWICHES.
WELL, YOU ALL KNOW
THAT I'M A PACIFIST
SO I'M NOT INTERESTED IN WAR
IN ANY WAY
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN THE REVOLUTION COMES,
I WILL HAVE TO DESTROY YOU ALL.
NOT YOU, JOEY.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]